It's exploration time!
Ready, set, go!
Mute style!
What's this? We've got ourselves a bit of a dilemma here.
Don't say that.
I haven't seen this duo since Tanabata.
That's right.
Speaking of which...
I'll let these two do the talking today.
I haven't told them yet.
I don't need that nonsense.
That's for the girls!
Please don't.
That's like the laugh from the first page of a textbook.
The project we have for you two today is...
Oh, my God.
Ten
Teareta NG
Burikko Expedition
What?
I didn't know about Teredo.
I couldn't do it.
I couldn't do it. I couldn't do it. I couldn't do it.
Yeah, I know.
Today, we're going to be doing a "Blicko Expedition.
Normally, we let everyone explore the museum as they are.
We usually let them explore eBean's, but...
That's fine, but...
But in order to make them more appealing...
We need more cuteness.
Certainly, it will be popular with everyone.
So, when I say "cute", I don't mean that you have to be cute.
I think that girls who are cute are the ones who are cute.
So today, I'm going to have the students explore the museum as if they were that girl.
I'm going to have them explore the museum.
Let's go!
Ready?
I want some!
Wait a minute.
I want some.
What's this?
Se-no-chan, what's this?
Do you want to make hot pot?
Do you want to make a pot?
I don't know...
In the morning and in the evening
There's so many of them.
What are you going to do?
Buy?
Let's buy some.
We'll be together.
You're gonna buy it?
I'll buy it.
2OOOO villager
Oh, stock
Armor.
This is 0 what?
Big Touma
I wonder if it's your birthday at the Stone Kiln Tourist Bar Lars.
Happy birthday to you.
A child of the forest?
So cute!
He's cute.
Smiling melon does it.
Deutsche.
Deuche.
Dwitch.
Doitch.
Looks like he's on Instagram and Twitter too.
You guys should follow him.
I know how to do it.
You don't know how to do that?
If you don't know how to do that, just open the camera and load it up.
Oh, that's a good one.
Oh, I found it.
What? What is this?
It's a hembou macatepecian.
There's a heart right here.
Wow, that's cute.
It's so cute.
What is this place?
Vomit river!
It's so cute!
He's so cute!
I'm sorry.
Strawberry marshmallow amen!
Can I have one of these, please?
One, please.
Not today.
Okay, then.
What should I do?
Hey...
Do you have any recommendations?
The rice cake drink of choice.
Brown sugar hojicha milk.
Hinoe, you forgot.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
Okay, then.
Your mom and your mom are gonna do this with me.
I'm looking forward to it.
Your sister, Chiming.
So cute.
Can I borrow some more?
Cute stuff.
Cute.
Give it to me.
Okay.
Yum!
Yummy!
It's not very cute.
I can't show you.
Oh, yummy!
I love it!
I wonder where we are.
Aah! What's that?
What is it?
I can't see. I can't see.
I can't run, I can't run.
He's cute.
Cute.
It's cute.
What's this?
What is that?
What is it?
What are these?
Because it's two things.
If there are two things...
Cherries.
Cherries!
You're a cherry, aren't you?
So cute!
You sell cherries?
We're in a fruit store.
A fruit stand.
Fruit shop.
You're going into a genre?
Yes, I see.
Cherries.
If you look here, you'll see what kind of cherries they are.
I can tell what kind.
I know what kind of cherries they are!
I know, Pao!
I know, I know!
Ready, set, go!
Happy smile
What's this place?
I like, like, like, like...
Mori no Iwate!
Yay!
Wow!
The world is so big.
Amazing!
Backwards.
Huh?
Hyuga.
Watch me.
Ready.
Amazing!
Oh, there's a bike.
Let's see...
I'm from the marshmallow planet.
Fluffy.
The cutest person in the world.
In the world?
In the universe
The cutest person in charge
Sakura
Pinano.
Wow!
Sakura.
Pinano
Wow.
Nice to meet you!
clap
I am a former dancer of YUKINKO KIDS
I'm a former dancer of Yukinko Kids and now a research student of Yukinko Kids.
Yuki Perorinchu
Churuchiruchin-choo
Churuchiruchinchotchi
Age is eternal 14 years old
My name is Miyu Puririn
Please do me a favor.
Please take care of us!
Please take care of us.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you, because I know so many of you will be here.
Thank you.Thank you.
Thank you.
I should go near you guys.
Maybe I should go.
I don't know if I can.
I'll send my spirit.
I'll send you a spirit.
Wow.
Thank you so much for coming out here today.
Thank you very much.
We wouldn't be able to do what we do if it weren't for you.
We wouldn't be able to do what we do.
Please continue to take care of us.
Even if you hate Mie.
But please don't hate me.
That's all I have to say.
Thank you for coming today.
Thank you also for that Coke drinker in the back.
Thank you.
Now let's talk about us.
All the way.
Have a good day!
Aoi, good night.
Okay.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's okay.
It's okay, right?
Like it was that hard for you.
You're tired?
I might have lost something.
I feel like I lost something important.
It's like every time I do something, something gets chipped away.
That's not true.
It was great.
At the end, there were already people at the Garden Fair.
There were a few of us.
And now I'm all alone.
As soon as you started talking...
I was in there.
I was wondering if there was anyone who stayed until the end today.
I was wondering...
I was curious. You should check it out.
But you're wrong.
That's what I'm saying.
There's no one cute.
They're gone.
No one with a pretty face.
I did today, but...
It's different.
I think it's interesting to do it as a character.
I think it's interesting.
I think this is good.
This is good.
I'm sure you'll get bored with it.
Good looking guys.
I'd love to play "handsome.
Can I buy you a drink?
Follow me.
I recommend this place.
They have the best toppings!
Your smile is sweeter than this dessert.
Oh!
But I'm sure we can do a lot of things.
If you have a character or something, leave it in the comment section.
YouTuber-like.
Let's do that kind of thing too.
That's all for today's exploration.
Please leave us, you two prissy kids.
Aren't you two pretties there?
Really?
They're back! I'm back!
I don't want to leave!
Hey, I still want to be with you.
Let's go home.